{
    "subject": "resource/Ken_Gillespie",
    "predicate": "property/awards",
    "object": "resource/Order_of_Australia",
    "human_readable": "Ken Gillespie has been awarded the Order of Australia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9871851801872253,
            "question": "When was Ken Gillespie awarded the Order of Australia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9112218618392944,
            "question": "Is Ken Gillespie Australian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8822868466377258,
            "question": "Who has been awarded the Order of Australia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8107234835624695,
            "question": "Name someone who has received the Order of Australia."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8086594939231873,
            "question": "What honor has Ken Gillespie received?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6368389129638672,
            "question": "What is a notable achievement of Ken Gillespie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4669858515262604,
            "question": "What is the significance of receiving the Order of Australia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4290257394313812,
            "question": "What does the Order of Australia recognize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35135331749916077,
            "question": "Are there different levels within the Order of Australia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2604796588420868,
            "question": "What are some examples of contributions that warrant the Order of Australia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ken Gillespie has been awarded the Order of Australia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2461_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there different levels within the Order of Australia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2461_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does the Order of Australia recognize?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2461_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of receiving the Order of Australia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2461_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2461_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2461_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2461_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2461_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2461_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2461_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2461_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2461_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2461_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2461_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents contain multiple references to Ken Gillespie being awarded the Companion of the Order of Australia (AC) for his service to the Australian Army and the country. Therefore, the information in the documents supports the triple that Ken Gillespie has been awarded the Order of Australia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that Lieutenant General Ken Gillespie was indeed awarded the Order of Australia. Specifically, multiple documents mention his receipt of the Companion of the Order of Australia (AC) for various services to the nation and the Australian Army."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}